[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "You really can't wait, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "You've never been ashamed about anything you've ever done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "You mean publicly or privately?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I don't -- well, let's go private.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, because I was young and dumb.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Whoopi"]}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "But if you are 40 -- are you about that age?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Don't flatter me, Whoopi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "May I ask?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "I just turned 46, but I'll take the first guess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Do you ever fear death yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, I think I must, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "You are afraid of flying, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, I don't like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Was there something that sparked it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "You saw it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yes, we saw it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Why is it so hard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, because what they discovered later on is that the people on the plane were aware that they were in some danger, but I think the person who was in the smaller plane had had a heart attack.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "You had a course, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "I had a course from the folks at virgin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Do you have other things that you're worried about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What foods?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, I don't like anything that has a weird consistency.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Cream corn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I don't understand the point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "You're allergic to cream corn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "No, I'm not allergic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "You're allergic to milk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "You can't drink milk and you can't eat cream corn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Because that's what it's called.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Why do you hate a cream corn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "I'm not and I want to be clear, I love corn.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "What, spinach?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Please, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I hate spinach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 212, "question": "You hate spinach?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Again, I appreciate the people who grow it and people --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 215, "question": "What are we left with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "You just live off fries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "No, no, no, I mean potato chips from the bag.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Can you eat meat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I do eat some meat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "You're really quite weird, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Isn't it great?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Cream corn is going to kill you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Do you think you were in love with all your husbands?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Any of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "It's an amazing thing to say, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "But it's the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "You won't -- you have church weddings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Why did you do it if you weren't in love with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Because I wanted to feel normal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "How my times have you been in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Who with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "A man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Can I chuck a name in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "You could chuck a name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Is that the man I'm talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Would we know who the person is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Is this a recent thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "You wish you'd married that person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Because what I know now is I don't want to live with -- I don't want to live with anyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Didn't you like being in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "OLDBERG: I don't know if I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Do you think that guy knows he's the only man you've ever loved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "You still talk to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Yes, we talk all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Are you -- are you on the dating scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Could you imagine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Do you get lonely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Are you disappointed that President Obama, who I know you're a massive fan of and supported, hasn't really done that much for gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm not surprised by it because, you know, very few presidents can go on and make the change they want to make.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Do you think we're getting there perhaps?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Well, listen, we didn't tip over the edge, in spite of the fact that, you know, everybody is saying, oh, he hasn't done anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "You were raised well by intelligent people for the most part, both of us, and that we know how to say to someone, would this bother you if I did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Going to take a little break now you're nicely fired up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Do you actually -- are you friends with the other co- stars of \"The View\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Or are they co-workers that you have to get on with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Often you looked like you haven't got the patience when you're out there with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Not with them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Don't you find Charlie Sheen's thing fascinating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Old torpedo winning duh thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "You had a problem with drugs, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Whatever you want to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "No, you know what, these are such personal issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Isn't it true that when you won your Oscar, you were actually high as a kite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Have you ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "No, God no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You've become really quite squeaky clean, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I still smoke cigarettes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "That I've gone after?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "You've gone after, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "What do you want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "OLDBERG: I say that's (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Is that ridiculous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Am I done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I didn't mean in a bad way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Did you ever think you'd be on TV every day giving opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "No, no, no, I never did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "When you hear Donald Trump go after Barack Obama for where he was born, what do you think about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "It makes me really, really angry.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think a lot of people will believe it anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Yes, they do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Is that the danger of that kind of politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, you know, it's not just the politics, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "How do you think you would have fared as a young celebrity when you first hit the big-time if the Internet had been around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Well, oh, yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I think you'd be surprised.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill O'Reilly", "Glenn Beck"]}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Who have I slapped around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Well, you know, if a politician is behaving in your view wrongly or if a right-wing cable host, someone like a Bill O'Reilly or Glenn Beck, whack, whack, whack.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "You're not defending him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps"]}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Because Michael Phelps is an Olympian athlete.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Or do you think that the drink loosens tongues, perhaps?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "I think that drunks say whatever comes into their head.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Do you ever get drunk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Once?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Yes, once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "You've been drunk once in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Once in my life, and I was in public.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Where was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "In New Orleans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How drunk were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Very drunk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "You don't think he has any responsibility as a role model?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "He's not smoking weed out in the street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Yes, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "So, no famous people should ever consider themselves to be role models?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "People -- famous people should consider themselves whatever they want to consider themselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "If you're a celebrity, and a few friends of yours have done this, if they sell their wedding for $1 million, are they entitled to privacy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "WP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "What did you want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Well, I wanted to say for those of you out there who disagree with me in terms of being a role model, save your e-mails.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "Are you going to be there for two more years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "Yes, as far as I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "Do you love it so much you want to carry on, or is there a natural shelf life to this thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "For the next 20 years you'd do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "I could do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "I'm not telling you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "You should have asked me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 798, "question": "A camel to -- OK, can we just talk about that, a camel to the oasis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", ":", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 799, "answer": "You can't take a camel to an oasis and then you say, you can't have a drink.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "ORGAN: What's on the horizon for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "Oh, you know, I've got musicals opening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "That's about white supremacists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "Is America more racist or less racist than, say, 20 years ago from your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "Because it just feels like questions to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 836, "question": "When you question this president, the first president we've ever had of color and you're not sure where he was born and it continues, is that about -- what is that about, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 837, "answer": "In Donald Trump's defense, I know him quite well, I don't think he's a racist at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RBR", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "Or Bill Clinton?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "I suspect it's about votes, because his poll ratings, the more he hammers this point -- it's probably an anti-Obama vote catching mechanism.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "Ever thought what heaven might be like when you get up there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "WP", "VBN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "I just assume it's going to be good times with the family, people that you didn't get to meet because they were gone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "Do you believe in an after life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Do you pray a lot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Probably?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 870, "question": "Well, no, I mean, it depends -- how do you describe praying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "I suppose --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 872, "question": "Going to church and stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 873, "answer": "Not necessarily going to church, but talking to an entity that is not physically there and asking for help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Do you do that kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "OLDBERG: No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "What's your idea of prayer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "I could use some backup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "Do you go to any church?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 883, "question": "At all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 884, "answer": "Very rarely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 912, "question": "And it can't be the birth of my kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 913, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 914, "question": "Or my grand kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 915, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "How about winning an Oscar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "That was very, very nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 941, "question": "Do you know who Moms Mabley was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 942, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April 20th"]}, "docId": "110416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "When does it open?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "OLDBERG: April 20th.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]